Sitting here with my head in my hands
手抚额前我坐在窗前
Ideas that come and go
想法接连显露
Sketching my heart out, nothing will turn out
用心画草稿，思绪全烦恼
Everything seems so-so
看起来都不够
I've been here before, and I know that I can
曾经这样过，我知道成果
Do it if I try
我能做出来
But why, oh, why
但唉，噢，唉
Do you stumble before you fly?
为何成功要先失败？
My wheels keep turnin'
我脚步不停
My fire's still burnin'
我燃烧热情
'Cause right now I'm learnin'
现在深学于心
How to get to the other side
如何到达灵感之外
It's a game of waitin'
等待心中不平
Anticipatin'
心期待不静
But I keep creatin'
但我创造不停
So I can get to the other, get to the other side
所以我能到达灵感，到达灵感之外
Get to the other side
到达灵感之外
So I can get to the other, get to the other...
所以我能到达灵感，到达灵感…
Keep on believin', I'll be achievin'
不断相信，再加把劲
The harder that I go
终能拔得头筹
Don't really know how, I won't give up now
就算不知道，也努力直到
Until I steal the show
真正出尽风头
With time, it gets better, I'll be a trendsetter
我一定要出色，潮流的领导者
Doin' it my own way
展示我的品味
Won't stop 'til I seize the day
不罢休直到夺魁
My wheels keep turnin'
我脚步不停
My fire's still burnin'
我燃烧热情
'Cause right now I'm learnin'
现在深学于心
How to get to the other side
如何到达灵感之外
It's a game of waitin'
等待心中不平
Anticipatin'
心期待不静
But I keep creatin'
但我创造不停
So I can get to the other, get to the other side
所以我能到达灵感，到达灵感之外
Get to the other side
到达灵感之外
So I can get to the other, get to the other side
所以我能到达灵感，到达灵感之外